Guide to the W. Keith Kennedy papers, 1971-1978.
Kennedy, W. Keith papers, 1971-1978.
Division of Rare and Manuscript Collections, Cornell University Library
W. Keith Kennedy papers, 1971-1978.
21-2-2764
W. Keith Kennedy, 1919-
47 cubic ft.
Administrative correspondence, reports, proposals, financial records, and other material.
Division of Rare and Manuscript Collections, Cornell University Library
Administrative correspondence, reports, proposals, financial records, and other material documenting the New York State College of Agriculture and Life Sciences at Cornell University and Kennedy's deanship from 1972to 1978.
BIOGRAPHICAL NOTE
W. Keith Kennedy was Dean of the New York State College of Agriculture and Life Sciences, 1972-1978.
COLLECTION DESCRIPTION
The papers of W. Keith Kennedy, Dean of the College of Agriculture and Life Sciences, consist chiefly of the routine administrative correspondence of the Dean's Office, and include reports, proposals, letters to and from the Dean, official communication between the Dean's Office and the College's departments and administrative units, and other material documenting the College's role at Cornell University, as part of the State University of New York, and in New York State and United States agriculture.
In addition to administrative correspondence with the many departments, programs, divisions, laboratories, and projects within the College, the papers show the College's attention to environmental concerns, responding to the needs and requests of numerous special interest organizations in New York State agriculture, and in relation to the state and federal governments (particularly the New York State Department of Agriculture and Markets, and the United States Department of Agriculture). The Dean's files reflect the era's concern with pesticides, water resources, special agricultural blights and afflictions, the 1972 flood, energy shortages, agricultural research and its financing, migrant labor and other social matters including affirmative action in the College and at Cornell, international agriculture, agribusiness and agricultural financing, the advancements in agricultural technology, agricultural law and legislation, the financing of higher education, soil conservation, and issues relating to food supply and food science.
At Cornell, the papers reflect on Dean Kennedy's meetings with deans and directors, the budgetary and financial operations of the College, the work of numerous College and University committees, Cornell University and SUNY Master Plans, major grant projects such as Sea Grant, the Cohn Farm controversy, department and division chairships, the New York State Agricultural Experiment Station at Geneva, the improvement of the College's physical plant and new buildings, the role of Cooperative Extension, questions of student deportment, relations with vice-presidents of Cornell and SUNY Vice-Chancellors, and the development of the Division of Biological Sciences.
In the Kennedy papers, principal organizations and businesses cited include Agway, Curtice-Burns Inc., and the American Agriculturist. At Cornell, departments and units include the Cornell University Board of Trustees, the Center for Environmental Quality Management, the Division of Biological Sciences, the Division of Nutritional Sciences, the Department of Education, the Graduate School, Cooperative Extension, International Agricultural Development, the Bailey Hortorium, the New York State Agricultural Experiment Station, the Department of Science, Technology, and Society, and the Water Resources and Marine Sciences Center. Regionally and nationally, principal organizations include the Ford Foundation, the Rockefeller Foundation, the National Science Foundation, the New York State College of Environmental Sciences and Forestry, the New York Farm Bureau, the New York State Department of Agriculture and Markets, the New York State Department of Environmental Conservation, the New York State Forest Practice Board, the State University of New York, the Northeast Center for Rural Development, the United States Department of Agriculture, and the United States Plant, Soil, and Nutrition Laboratory.
Major correspondents include: J. Robert Barlow, Mark Barlow, Nyle C. Brady, Dale R. Corson, Bruce Dearing, Laing E. Kennedy, David C. Knapp, R. D. O'Brien, and Charles E. Palm.
SUBJECTS
Names:
Kennedy, W. Keith, 1919-; Barlow, Mark.; Brady, Nyle C.; O'Brien, R. D.; Palm, Charles E.; Agway, Inc.; Cornell University--Administration.; Cornell University. Cooperative Extension.; Cornell University. Division of Biological Sciences.; New York (State). Department of Agriculture and Markets.; New York State College of Agriculture and Life Sciences--Administration.; New York State College of Agriculture and Life Sciences. Agricultural Experiment Station.; New York State. Agricultural Experiment Station.; State University of New York.; United States. Department of Agriculture.
Subjects:
Environmentalism--New York (State); Agriculture--Study and teaching.; Agricultural laborers.; Agricultural extension work--New York (State); Agricultural laws and legislation--New York (State); Agriculture--Economic aspects.; Agricultural ecology.; Agriculture and energy.; Agriculture--Research.; Agriculture and state.
INFORMATION FOR USERS
Access Restrictions:
Restricted to permission of the Office of Origin.
COLLECTION ARRANGEMENT
The papers of Dean Keith Kennedy were arranged in approximate academic year spans, with an alphabetical listing of folder headings. These originally titled folder headings and the Dean's Office classification system have been in all cases retained.
Some topics and organizations are listed variably and informally: University Senate rather than Cornell University Senate, or Senate. Committees are listed as they were familiarly called by the Dean's office, in either natural or formal order: Floriculture rather than the Department of Floriculture and Ornamental Horticulture: Provost's Office rather than Office of the Provost. Some subheadings are indistinct: whether agencies were Cornell, New York State, or U.S. was undifferentiated by the Dean's Office. Moreover, departments of the College of Agriculture and Life Sciences and Cornell University are variably listed in the index as they were in the guide. Nominal attribution is also informal: some acronyms are unspecified, and some first names are lacking.
CONTAINER LIST
- Circular Letters, 1972-1973 (Box 1, Folder 1-2)
- Assistant to the Dean (Kennedy, Laing E.), 1972-1973 (Box 1, Folder 3)
- Associate Dean (Brady, Dr.), 1972-1973 (Box 1, Folder 4)
- Associate Dean (Spencer, James), 1973 (Box 1, Folder 5)
- Coordinator of Planning (Kent, G. C.), 1973 (Box 1, Folder 6-7)
- Palm, Charles E., 1972-1973 (Box 1, Folder 8)
- Agricultural Economics, 1972-1973 (Box 1, Folder 9-13)
- Agricultural Economics--Chairmanship, 1972-1973 (Box 1, Folder 14)
- Economic Situation, Current, 1972 (Box 1, Folder 15)
- Agricultural Engineering, 1972-1973 (Box 1, Folder 16-18)
- Agronomy, 1972-1973 (Box 1, Folder 19-22)
- Animal Science, 1972-1973 (Box 1, Folder 23-25)
- Bailey Hortorium, 1972-1973 (Box 1, Folder 26)
- Dairy Report, 1972 (Box 1, Folder 27)
- CSCS (Cassette Special Communication Systems), 1973 (Box 1, Folder 28)
- Communication Arts, 1972-1973 (Box 1, Folder 29-31)
- Ward, William B., 1973 (Box 1, Folder 32)
- Education, 1972-1973 (Box 1, Folder 33-36)
- Education Chairmanship, 1973 (Box 1, Folder 37)
- Vocational and Technical Education Schools, 1972 (Box 1, Folder 38)
- Entomology, 1972-1973 (Box 1, Folder 39-43)
- Pesticide Residue Laboratory, 1972-1973 (Box 1, Folder 44)
- Entomology Headship, 1972-1973 (Box 1, Folder 45-46)
- Axtell, Richard C., 1972-1973 (Box 1, Folder 47)
- Axtell, Richard C., Publications, 1972-1973 (Box 1, Folder 48-50)
- Hodgson, Ernest, 1972 (Box 1, Folder 51)
- McEwen, F. L., 1972 (Box 1, Folder 52)
- Entomology, 1972 (Box 2, Folder 1)
- Traub, Robert, 1972 (Box 2, Folder 2)
- Cooperative Extension, 1972 (Box 2, Folder 3-11)
- Cooperative Extension, 1973 (Box 2, Folder 12-17)
- County Extension Agents, 1972-1973 (Box 2, Folder 18)
- 4-H, 1972-1973 (Box 2, Folder 19)
- Program Planning and Development--Cooperative Extension, 1973 (Box 2, Folder 20)
- Cooperative Extension, 1972-1973 (Box 2, Folder 21-22)
- Extension Tour--Capital District, 1972-1973 (Box 2, Folder 23)
- Cooperative Extension, 1971 (Box 2, Folder 24)
- Finance and Business, 1972-1973 (Box 2, Folder 25-27)
- Floriculture, 1972-1973 (Box 2, Folder 28-34)
- Food Science, 1972-1973 (Box 2, Folder 35-37)
- Chairmanship in Food Science, 1972 (Box 2, Folder 38)
- Geneva, 1972-1973 (Box 2, Folder 39-46)
- Institute of Food Science and Marketing, 1972-1973 (Box 2, Folder 47-49)
- I A D (International Agricultural Development), 1972-1973 (Box 3, Folder 1-3)
- I A D--Schedule for Prof. Harrar, J. G., 1972 (Box 3, Folder 4)
- Mann Library, 1972-1973 (Box 3, Folder 5)
- Natural Resources, 1972-1973 (Box 3, Folder 6-10)
- Arnot Forest, 1972-1973 (Box 3, Folder 11)
- Biothermal Laboratory, 1972 (Box 3, Folder 12)
- Plant Breeding and Biometry, 1972-1973 (Box 3, Folder 13-14)
- Plant Pathology, 1972-1973 (Box 3, Folder 15-19)
- Pomology, 1972-1973 (Box 3, Folder 20-21)
- Poultry Science, 1972-1973 (Box 3, Folder 22-24)
- Research, 1972-1973 (Box 3, Folder 25-27)
- Search for Director of Research, 1973 (Box 3, Folder 28)
- Resident Instruction, 1972-1973 (Box 3, Folder 28-32)
- Rural Sociology, 1972-1973 (Box 3, Folder 33-36)
- Vegetable Crops, 1972-1973 (Box 3, Folder 37-38)
- Vegetable Crops Candidates, 1972-1973 (Box 3, Folder 39)
- Statements, 1972-1973 (Box 3, Folder 40-43)
- Interdepartmental, 1972-1973 (Box 3, Folder 44-46)
- Requisitions, 1972-1973 (Box 3, Folder 47-54)
- Travel Reimbursements, 1972-1973 (Box 4, Folder 1)
- Agricultural Leaders' Forum, 1962-1972 (Box 4, Folder 2-3)
- Council for the New York State College of Agriculture, 1940-1959 (Box 4, Folder 11-Apr)
- Assistant to the President (Barlow, J. Robert. Robert;), 1972-1973 (Box 4, Folder 12)
- Assistant to the President (Hall, Jackson O.), 1972 (Box 4, Folder 13)
- Assistant to the Provost (Jones, William D.), 1972 (Box 4, Folder 14)
- Cornell University Board of Trustees, 1972-1973 (Box 4, Folder 15-17)
- Controller, 1972-1973 (Box 4, Folder 18)
- University Counsel, 1972-1973 (Box 4, Folder 19)
- Dean of the Faculty (Penney, Norman), 1972-1973 (Box 4, Folder 20)
- President's Office (Corson, Dale R.), 1972-1973 (Box 4, Folder 21)
- Provost (Plane, Robert A. and Knapp, David C.), 1972-1973 (Box 4, Folder 22)
- Treasurer, 1972-1973 (Box 4, Folder 23)
- Vice President for Administration, 1972-1973 (Box 4, Folder 24)
- Vice President for Planning, 1972-1973 (Box 4, Folder 25)
- Vice President for Public Affairs, 1972-1973 (Box 4, Folder 26)
- Vice President for Research, 1972-1973 (Box 4, Folder 27)
- Vice President for Student Affairs (Gurowitz, William), 1972-1973 (Box 4, Folder 28)
- Vice Provost (McKeegan, Paul L.), 1972-1973 (Box 4, Folder 29)
- Vice Provost (Risley, Robert F.), 1972-1973 (Box 4, Folder 30-31)
- "Born Losers", 1972-1973 (Box 4, Folder 32)
- Deans and Directors (D & D)--Agendas, 1972-1973 (Box 4, Folder 33)
- D & D--Minutes, 1972-1973 (Box 4, Folder 34-35)
- Dean's Council, 1972-1973 (Box 4, Folder 36)
- Department Heads' Meetings, 1972-1973 (Box 4, Folder 37)
- Statutory Deans' Meetings, 1972-1973 (Box 4, Folder 38)
- SUNY--Administrative Services (Spaner, Arnold), 1972-1973 (Box 4, Folder 39)
- SUNY--Board of Trustees, 1972-1973 (Box 4, Folder 40-43)
- SUNY--Director of Budgets (Anslow, William H.), 1972-1973 (Box 4, Folder 44)
- SUNY--President's Budget, 1973 (Box 4, Folder 45)
- SUNY--Campus Development (Gassman, M. C.), 1972-1973 (Box 4, Folder 46)
- SUNY--Campus Relations (Block, Murray), 1973 (Box 4, Folder 47)
- SUNY--Chancellor (Boyer, Ernest L.), 1972-1973 (Box 4, Folder 48)
- SUNY--Council of Presidents, 1972-1973 (Box 4, Folder 49-53)
- SUNY--Enrollments, 1972-1973 (Box 4, Folder 54)
- SUNY--Faculty Senate, 1972-1973 (Box 4, Folder 55)
- SUNY--Governmental Relations, 1972-1973 (Box 4, Folder 56)
- SUNY--Graduate Review, 1973 (Box 5, Folder 1)
- SUNY--Graduate Council, 1972-1973 (Box 5, Folder 2-9)
- SUNY--Graduate Studies, 1972-1973 (Box 5, Folder 10)
- SUNY--Higher Education Amendments, 1972 (Box 5, Folder 11)
- SUNY--Institutional Research, 1972-1973 (Box 5, Folder 12)
- SUNY--International Programs, 1972-1973 (Box 5, Folder 13)
- SUNY--Marine Sciences, 1972-1973 (Box 5, Folder 14)
- SUNY--Miscellaneous, 1972-1973 (Box 5, Folder 15)
- SUNY--Monthly Reports of Campus Activities, 1972-1973 (Box 5, Folder 16)
- SUNY--News Letters, 1972-1973 (Box 5, Folder 17)
- SUNY--Policy and Planning (Ingler, Charles W.), 1972-1973 (Box 5, Folder 18)
- SUNY--Presidents (Campus) Meetings, 1972-1973 (Box 5, Folder 19)
- SUNY--Provost for Research and Graduate Study (Murray, Daniel), 1972-1973 (Box 5, Folder 20)
- SUNY--Stonybrook, 1972-1973 (Box 5, Folder 21)
- SUNY--Transfer Admissions, 1972 (Box 5, Folder 22)
- SUNY--Tuition, 1972-1973 (Box 5, Folder 23)
- SUNY--25th Anniversary, 1972-1973 (Box 5, Folder 24)
- SUNY--University Counsel, 1972-1973 (Box 5, Folder 25)
- SUNY--Vice Chancellor for Academic Programs (Dearing, Bruce), 1972-1973 (Box 5, Folder 26)
- SUNY--Vice Chancellor for Finance, Management and Business (Spindler, Harry K.), 1972-1973 (Box 5, Folder 27)
- SUNY--Vice Chancellor for Personnel and Employee Relations (Egerton, J. W.), 1972-1973 (Box 5, Folder 28)
- SUNY--Vice Chancellor for University Affairs (Thorne, Clifton C.), 1972-1973 (Box 5, Folder 29)
- SUNY--University-Wide Services and Special Programs, 1972-1973 (Box 5, Folder 30)
- SUNY--Agriculture and Technical Colleges, 1972-1973 (Box 5, Folder 31)
- SUNY--Binghamton, 1972-1973 (Box 5, Folder 32)
- SUNY--Empire State College, 1972-1973 (Box 5, Folder 33)
- Biological Sciences--Accessory Instruction, 1972-1973 (Box 5, Folder 34)
- Biological Sciences (O'Brien, R. D.), 1972-1973 (Box 5, Folder 35-38)
- Biological Sciences--Executive Committee Meetings, 1972-1973 (Box 5, Folder 39)
- Biological Sciences--Blackler Course (Blackler, Tonie), 1972-1973 (Box 5, Folder 40)
- Cell Laboratory, 1972-1973 (Box 5, Folder 41)
- Biochemistry and Molecular Biology, 1972-1973 (Box 5, Folder 42)
- (Steward, F. C.)--Symposium, 1973 (Box 5, Folder 43)
- Ecology, 1972-1973 (Box 5, Folder 44)
- Genetics, Development, and Physiology, 1972-1973 (Box 5, Folder 45)
- Microbiology, 1972-1973 (Box 5, Folder 46)
- Microbiology Advisory Committee, 1972-1973 (Box 5, Folder 47)
- Division of Biological Sciences--Neurobiology and Behavior, 1972-1973 (Box 5, Folder 48)
- Wiegand Herbarium, 1972-1973 (Box 5, Folder 49)
- (Palm, Charles)--Papers, 1961-1972 (Box 5, Folder 50-51)
- Correspondence--A, 1972-1973 (Box 5, Folder 52)
- Office of Academic Funding (Research), 1972-1973 (Box 5, Folder 53)
- Accounts--College of Agriculture, 1972-1973 (Box 5, Folder 54)
- Admissions, 1972-1973 (Box 5, Folder 55)
- Affirmative Action Program, 1972-1973 (Box 5, Folder 56)
- Agribusiness Council, 1972-1973 (Box 5, Folder 57)
- Agriculture Fund, 1972-1973 (Box 5, Folder 58-61)
- Agricultural Labor Relations Specialist Search Committee, 1972-1973 (Box 5, Folder 62)
- Agricultural Leaders' Forum, 1973 (Box 5, Folder 63)
- New York State Agricultural Resource Commission, 1972-1973 (Box 5, Folder 64)
- Council for Agricultural Science and Technology, 1972-1973 (Box 5, Folder 65)
- Agricultural Stabilization and Conservation Service (A S C), 1972-1973 (Box 5, Folder 66)
- Agricultural Statistics, 1972-1973 (Box 5, Folder 67-69)
- Agricultural Waste Management, 1972-1973 (Box 6, Folder 1)
- New York State Department of Agriculture and Markets, 1972-1973 (Box 6, Folder 2)
- International Agronomy Award, 1972-1973 (Box 6, Folder 3)
- Agway, 1972-1973 (Box 6, Folder 4-5)
- Agriculture and Life Sciences Development Fund, 1972-1973 (Box 6, Folder 6)
- Alumni Affairs, 1972-1973 (Box 6, Folder 7)
- Alumni Association--College of Ag & Life Sciences, 1972-1973 (Box 6, Folder 8)
- Alumni Fund Drive, 1972-1973 (Box 6, Folder 9)
- American Agriculturist, 1972-1973 (Box 6, Folder 10)
- American Society of Agronomy, 1972-1973 (Box 6, Folder 11)
- Apple Growers Association, 1972-1973 (Box 6, Folder 12)
- Apple Pest Management Program, 1972-1973 (Box 6, Folder 13)
- Aquatic Animal Research and Education Center, 1972-1973 (Box 6, Folder 14)
- College of Architecture, Art and Planning, 1972-1973 (Box 6, Folder 15)
- College of Arts and Sciences, 1972-1973 (Box 6, Folder 16)
- Assistantships, 1972-1973 (Box 6, Folder 17)
- Astronomy Department, 1972-1973 (Box 6, Folder 18)
- "At a Glance", 1972-1973 (Box 6, Folder 19)
- Athletics, 1972-1973 (Box 6, Folder 20)
- Audio-Visual, 1972-1973 (Box 6, Folder 21)
- Awards, 1972-1973 (Box 6, Folder 22)
- Correspondence--B, 1972-1973 (Box 6, Folder 23)
- Bankhead-Jones, 1972-1973 (Box 6, Folder 24)
- Boyce Thompson Institute for Plant Research, 1972-1973 (Box 6, Folder 25)
- Brochure, Ag & Life Sciences, 1972-1973 (Box 6, Folder 26)
- Budget, 1972-1973 (Box 6, Folder 27)
- Division of the Budget, 1972-1973 (Box 6, Folder 28)
- Budget Hearings, 1972-1973 (Box 6, Folder 29)
- Building and Properties, 1972-1973 (Box 6, Folder 30)
- Bursar, 1972-1973 (Box 6, Folder 31)
- Correspondence--C, 1972-1973 (Box 6, Folder 32)
- Calendar, 1972-1973 (Box 6, Folder 33)
- Canadarago Lake Watershed, 1972-1973 (Box 6, Folder 34)
- Carey Estate, 1972-1973 (Box 6, Folder 35)
- Council for Agricultural Society and Technology (CAST), 1972-1973 (Box 6, Folder 36)
- Catskill Mountains, 1972-1973 (Box 6, Folder 37)
- Chemicals, 1972-1973 (Box 6, Folder 38)
- Chemistry Department, 1972-1973 (Box 6, Folder 39)
- Chenango Development Project, 1972-1973 (Box 6, Folder 40)
- City Program, New York City, 1972-1973 (Box 6, Folder 41)
- Civil Rights Compliance Review, 1972-1973 (Box 6, Folder 42)
- Climatologist, 1972-1973 (Box 6, Folder 43)
- Community Resource Development Program Review, 1972-1973 (Box 6, Folder 44)
- Computers, 1972-1973 (Box 6, Folder 45)
- Conference on Computer Satellites, 1972 (Box 6, Folder 46)
- Conservation Leaders' Forum, 1972-1973 (Box 6, Folder 47)
- Continuing Education, 1972-1973 (Box 6, Folder 48)
- Cooperative Extension Specialists, 1972-1973 (Box 6, Folder 49)
- Coordinating Areas, 1972-1973 (Box 6, Folder 50)
- Cornell Fund, 1972-1973 (Box 6, Folder 51)
- Cornell Plantations, 1972-1973 (Box 6, Folder 52)
- Cornell-State Relations, 1972-1973 (Box 6, Folder 53)
- COSEP, 1972-1973 (Box 6, Folder 54)
- COSPA / NY, 1972-1973 (Box 6, Folder 55)
- Council of Agricultural Organizations, 1972-1973 (Box 6, Folder 56)
- Curtice-Burns, Inc., 1972-1973 (Box 6, Folder 57)
- Correspondence--D, 1972-1973 (Box 6, Folder 58)
- Dairy Extension Program, 1972-1973 (Box 6, Folder 59)
- Dairy Herd Improvement, 1972-1973 (Box 6, Folder 60)
- New York Dairy Farm Business Summary, 1972 (Box 6, Folder 61)
- Dean's List, 1972-1973 (Box 6, Folder 62)
- University Development, 1972-1973 (Box 6, Folder 63)
- Diagnostic Laboratory, 1972-1973 (Box 6, Folder 64)
- Correspondence--E, 1972-1973 (Box 6, Folder 65)
- East-West Communication Institute, 1972-1973 (Box 6, Folder 66)
- Economics, 1972-1973 (Box 6, Folder 67)
- New York State Education Department, 1972-1973 (Box 6, Folder 68)
- Office of Educational Development, 1972-1973 (Box 6, Folder 69)
- Effort Reporting, 1972-1973 (Box 6, Folder 70)
- Einstein Professorship, 1972-1973 (Box 6, Folder 71)
- Electrification Council of New York, 1972-1973 (Box 6, Folder 72)
- Empire State Farm Days, 1972-1973 (Box 6, Folder 73)
- Empire State Potato Club, Inc., 1972-1973 (Box 6, Folder 74)
- Cornell Energy Project, 1972-1973 (Box 6, Folder 75)
- Energy Crisis, 1972-1973 (Box 6, Folder 76)
- College of Engineering, 1972-1973 (Box 6, Folder 77)
- Educational Opportunity Program (EOP), 1972-1973 (Box 6, Folder 78)
- Equal Program Opportunity (EOP), 1972-1973 (Box 6, Folder 79)
- College of Environmental Sciences and Forestry, 1972-1973 (Box 6, Folder 80)
- SUNY--College of Environmental Science and Forestry, 1971-1973 (Box 6, Folder 81-83)
- Correspondence--F, 1972-1973 (Box 6, Folder 84)
- Finger Lakes Conservancy, 1972-1973 (Box 6, Folder 85)
- Fireblight, 1972-1973 (Box 6, Folder 86)
- Eastern Fish Disease Laboratory, 1972-1973 (Box 6, Folder 87)
- New York State Fish and Wildlife Management Board, 1972-1973 (Box 6, Folder 88)
- Fleet Office, 1972-1973 (Box 6, Folder 89)
- Flood, 1972, 1972-1973 (Box 6, Folder 90-91)
- Flood Control Program, 1972-1973 (Box 6, Folder 92)
- Ford Foundation, 1972-1973 (Box 7, Folder 1)
- Full-Time Equivalents (FTE), 1972-1973 (Box 7, Folder 2)
- Correspondence--G, 1972-1973 (Box 7, Folder 3)
- General Foods, 1972-1973 (Box 7, Folder 4)
- General Services, 1972-1973 (Box 7, Folder 5)
- Girton Manufacturing Company, 1972-1973 (Box 7, Folder 6)
- Graduate Activity, 1972-1973 (Box 7, Folder 7)
- Graduate Faculty, 1972-1973 (Box 7, Folder 8)
- Graduate School, 1972-1973 (Box 7, Folder 9)
- Correspondence--H, 1972-1973 (Box 7, Folder 10)
- Health, Education and Welfare Department, 1972-1973 (Box 7, Folder 11)
- Higher Education and National Affairs Publication, 1972-1973 (Box 7, Folder 12)
- Joint Legislative Committee on Higher Education, 1972-1973 (Box 7, Folder 13)
- Ho-Nun-De-Kah, 1972-1973 (Box 7, Folder 14)
- Horse, 1972-1973 (Box 7, Folder 15)
- Housing, 1972-1973 (Box 7, Folder 16)
- Hudson River Basin, 1972-1973 (Box 7, Folder 17)
- Hudson Valley Research Laboratory, 1972-1973 (Box 7, Folder 18-21)
- Human Affairs Program (HAP), 1972-1973 (Box 7, Folder 22)
- New York State College of Human Ecology, 1972-1973 (Box 7, Folder 23)
- Correspondence--I, 1972-1973 (Box 7, Folder 24)
- Intercultural Awareness and Training, 1972-1973 (Box 7, Folder 25)
- Industrial and Labor Relations (ILR), 1972-1973 (Box 7, Folder 26)
- ILR--Local Government Programs, 1972-1973 (Box 7, Folder 27-28)
- International Student Office, 1972-1973 (Box 7, Folder 29)
- Center for International Studies, 1972-1973 (Box 7, Folder 30-32)
- Irrigation Systems, 1972-1973 (Box 7, Folder 33)
- Correspondence--J, 1972-1973 (Box 7, Folder 34)
- Correspondence--K, 1972-1973 (Box 7, Folder 35)
- Correspondence--L, 1972-1973 (Box 7, Folder 36)
- Land Runoffs--Communications Task Force, 1972-1973 (Box 7, Folder 37)
- Livestock Material, 1972-1973 (Box 7, Folder 38)
- Long Island (Riverhead and Farmingdale), 1972-1973 (Box 7, Folder 39)
- Members of Assembly, 1972-1973 (Box 7, Folder 40)
- Buckley and Carroll's visit (Buckley, James and Carroll, Joan), 1972-1973 (Box 7, Folder 41)
- Congressmen, 1972-1973 (Box 7, Folder 42)
- Andrews, Congressman Mark, 1972-1973 (Box 7, Folder 43)
- Riford, Assemblyman Lloyd, 1972-1973 (Box 7, Folder 44)
- Governor's Office, 1972-1973 (Box 7, Folder 45)
- Senators, 1972-1973 (Box 7, Folder 46)
- Javits, Senator Jacob K., 1972-1973 (Box 7, Folder 47)
- Correspondence--M, 1972-1973 (Box 7, Folder 48)
- Management Systems and Analysis, 1972-1973 (Box 7, Folder 49)
- Massena Area Tour, 1972 (Box 7, Folder 50)
- Maternity Leave Policy, 1972-1973 (Box 7, Folder 51)
- Media Center, 1972-1973 (Box 7, Folder 52)
- Cornell Medical College, 1972-1973 (Box 7, Folder 53)
- Meteorology, 1972-1973 (Box 7, Folder 54)
- New York State Migrant Center, 1972-1973 (Box 7, Folder 55)
- Miner Institute, 1972-1973 (Box 7, Folder 56)
- Mining and Minerals Resources Research Act, 1972-1973 (Box 7, Folder 57)
- Minority Employment, 1972-1973 (Box 7, Folder 58)
- Correspondence--Mc, 1972-1973 (Box 7, Folder 59)
- Correspondence--N, 1972-1973 (Box 7, Folder 60)
- National Association of State Universities and Land Grant Colleges (NASULGC) Meeting, 1972 (Box 7, Folder 61)
- NASULGC--Council of Administrative Heads for Agricultural Colleges, 1972-1973 (Box 7, Folder 62-64)
- NASULGC, 1972-1973 (Box 7, Folder 65)
- NASULGC--Suit Against, 1972-1973 (Box 7, Folder 66)